# BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

## Nahuel Brandán

EMAIL: contact@nahuelbrandan.com | WEB: www.nahuelbrandan.com/en |







### ABOUT ME 🔿

Backend Software Developer, specialized in the Python ecosystem, with more than 3 years of experience in the industry, ultimately working in the aerospace industry.

I am passionate about turning ideas into functional products through software, going through the different stages of development and promoting good practices. Always in constant learning.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **BACKEND SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

**Company: Satellogic** | 06/2022 - 09/2022

Company specialized in earth observation satellites. Design, manufacture, and operate his own fleet of satellites.

I was part of the backend development team, based on Python, of satellite flight applications, dealing with highly complex problems.

#### Company: Ascentio Technologies | Project: Sabia-Mar | 08/2021 - 05/2022

Sabia-Mar is a satellite mission, with advanced technology for the study of the sea and the ocean.

I worked as a software developer in **Python**, making contributions to different communication and flight planning modules of the satellite. Developer of both the software and the validation tests. Working with technologies like: Robot Framework, Docker, FastAPI, Django, APIs.

#### **Company:** <u>IncluIT</u> | **Project:** <u>Junar</u> | 03/2019 - 07/2021

- Performing development activities in Python + Django + Django Rest Framework.
- Integration of Autho and Keyclok as a security layer to an API Management.
- Development related to **Elastic Search**, **Redis**, **Celery**.

#### EDUCATION (

#### **BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN COMPUTER ANALYST - (COMPLETED)**

#### Faculty of Mathematics, Astronomy, Physics and Computing - UNC | 10/2018

Career with strong emphasis on programming, analysis and design of systems, databases and computer networks, without neglecting the theoretical aspects that sustain them.

#### SELF-STUDY ONLINE COURSES | Platzi | 01/2021 - Present

More than **100 courses completed** and in constant learning in the Platzi professional online academy, on various topics such as: soft skills, English, software development.

#### SKILLS (

- Programming languages: Python, C.
- Databases: MySQL, MongoDB, Redis, Elastic Search.
- Frameworks: Django, FastAPI, Robot FW.
- Others: Linux, API Rest, Django, Git, Bash, Autho, Docker, FastAPI, Robot FW.

#### EXTRAS C

English: B1 intermediate.

• Spanish: Native.







